# MARAM MUBARAK



# SAP CONSULTANT

# **EXPERTISE**



**PROGRAMMING** 

FRONT END DESIGN

**BACK END DESIGN** 

**CMMI DOCUMENTATION** 

**MARKETING** 

# TECH SKILLS



SAP (ABAP, SMARTFORMS, WEBDYNPRO, ENTERPRISE PORTAL)

SQL, ORACLE

C, C++, C#, VB, ASP.NET

DESKTOP SUPPORT





# PROFILE

Highly skilled and hardworking Developer with a superb work ethic and client satisfaction record. I have Experience in full life-cycle SAP projects involving implementations and support. I possess excellent problem-solving skills with the ability to locate the source of the problem and then find a feasible solution in a fast and efficient manner. I also have the ability to maintain a friendly and professional attitude when working under stressful conditions and to stay focused in order to meet deadlines



# EXPERIENCE

## APPLICATION DEVELOPER (Freelance)

JAN 2017 – CURRENT Working in different domains of software and IT infrastructure development such as web development, .NET, SAP ABAP, SAP WF and developing print design such as brochures and posters.

## ACCOUNT MANAGER Transformed Net Co. (Freelance)

APR 2016 - NOV 2016 responsible for the management of sales and relationships with customers.

#### MY RESPONSIBILITIES INCLUDED:

- Identify new sales opportunities.
- Scheduled appointments and developed good customer relationships.
- Developed various business proposals and prepared necessary presentations accordingly.

# CALL CENTER AGENT SamrtLink Co. (Freelance)

**FEB 2016 – MAR 2016** Working as call center agent for Al Ajlan Bro Co in contract with smartlink.

### SAP CONSULTANT Systems of Strategic Business Solutions

**DEC 2010 – AUG 2014** Working as ABAP developer for Saudi Aramco projects in contract with SSBS

#### **PROJECTS:**

- D&WO Hauling Automation Process Saudi Aramco
   Technology Used: WebDynpro for ABAP, SAP Workflow, SAP ABAP,
   SAP Portal. Nov 2010 April 2011
- Plant Operation Information Systems Saudi Aramco
  Technology Used: SAP WebDynpro Java Programming, SAP NWDS,
  Hibernate, Apache FOP, XML. Jun 2011 Jun 2012

## IT HELP DESK AGENT Mena Business Services

**APR 2009 – NOV 2010** Working as a helpdesk Provider in the IT Help Desk held in Saudi Aramco in contract with MBS.

#### MY RESPONSIBILITIES INCLUDED:

- Resolving problems in all areas of IT
- Creating and categorizing problem tickets using Remedy System



# EDUCATION

BACHELOR IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

KING SAUD UNIVERSITY GPA: 4.34 out of 5 with 2ed Class of Honor

